Finding Aid for James W. Toy Papers 1963-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical files
  Another committee represented in this series is the Committee on Lesbian and Gay Concerns. Included here are the committee's correspondence, minutes, press releases, questionnaires, and resolutions. The series also contains records relating to Toy's involvement with the Ann Arbor-Ypsilanti Chapter of the Gay, Lesbian, and Straight Education Network (GLSEN). Within this part of the series, minutes and correspondence are combined together because they are both included within the e-mails that members sent to each other. In addition, the series contains a small section of personal materials, including a Biographical folder, Correspondence folder, and a Miscellaneous folder. The Biographical folder contains information on Toy's life and a CD-ROM entitled "Jim Toy: A Celebration of Community Liberation." The Miscellaneous folder contains notes from an unknown event and collected publications from Michigan human rights organizations. There are a couple of folders in the series dedicated to the Ypsilanti Human Rights Political Action Committee. One folder contains correspondence and minutes of the committee, while the other contains correspondence and minutes of Rainbow Neighbors (which was a part of the Ypsilanti Human Rights Political Action Committee).
  - Ackerman, Gary (poetry and essays) (Box 9)
  - AIDS
    - Action Against AIDS/Ann Arbor (later AIDS Action Alliance, Ann Arbor) 1985-1986 (Box 9)
    - AIDS-related Communication Coalition 1986 (Box 9)
    - AIDS 101: A University of Michigan Health Services Peer Education Program 1987 (Box 9)
    - AIDS: Implications for Social Service Professionals conference December 1985, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Coping with AIDS conference December 1985 (Box 9)
    - Course: AIDS: The Challenge to Society 1990-1994 (Box 9)
    - Course papers 1981, 1986, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Healing AIDS conference December 1993 (Box 9)
    - Published materials/clippings (Box 9)
    - U-M AIDS Task Force/U-M-related 1986-1988, undated (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - American Civil Liberties Union of Michigan 1973-1986 (mainly pertaining to Committee on Lesbian Women and Gay Men, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - American Psychiatric Association 1974 (position regarding homosexuality) (Box 9)
  - Ann Arbor Area Association for Civil Concerns (formerly Ann Arbor Gay/Lesbian Organization) 1982-1983 (4 folders) (Box 9)
  - Ann Arbor Gay Community Services 1980-1981 (see also Gay Community Services, a separate organization) (Box 9)
  - Ann Arbor Gay Discussion Group 1980-1982 (Box 9)
  - Ann Arbor Gay Programs Collective 1979 (Box 9)
  - Ann Arbor Gays (essays, incident at the Rubaiyat restaurant) (Box 9)
  - Announcements of events (flyers, etc.)
    (see also oversize posters in box 22)
    - Ann Arbor and environs, general, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Ann Arbor and environs, general, 1 folder (Box 10)
    - Michigan, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - National/Out-of-state (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Anti-gay/crank materials (Box 10)
  - Anti-Sexism Center (Box 10)
  - Anti-Violence and Discrimination Task Force undated (Box 10)
  - Association of Suburban People 1978-1982 (Box 10)
  - Baker, Deane (U-M regent) (Box 10)
  - Bibliographies, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Biron, Lionel (Box 10)
  - Bisexuality 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Campus Information Center (Box 10)
  - Campus security (complaints directed toward) 1981-1984 (Box 10)
  - Central Michigan University (Box 10)
  - Classes conducted
    - Gay Issues in Social Work (later Lesbian and Gay Issues in Social Work 1978-1979, 1984 (2 folders and 1 expandable folder) (Box 10)
    - Human Sexuality (INTEFLEX class) 1986-1991 (Box 10)
    - Lesbian-child custody 1976 (Box 10)
    - Women and the community (internship program) 1985 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Class papers and projects re lesbians and gay males, 3 folders (Box 10)
  - Clippings, undated 1962, 1970-1994, 19 folders (Box 11)
  - Colorado boycott 1993 (Box 11)
  - Coming-out 1978-1992 (Box 11)
  - Conferences/workshops
    - Undated-fragmentary (Box 11)
    - 1970s general (Box 11)
    - 1972. Human Sexuality (Box 11)
    - 1973 (June). Human Sexuality (Box 11)
    - 1974-1975. Sexuality: an expression of self (Box 11)
    - 1975. Planning programs in human sexuality (Box 11)
    - 1978. Gay lifestyles (Box 11)
    - 1980s general (Box 11)
    - 1980. Homosexuality in perspective (Box 11)
    - 1980-1981. Dorm staff (Box 11)
    - 1981. Working with gay male clients (Box 11)
    - 1981. Stress in the university (Box 11)
    - 1982-1985. Exploring gay issues (includes some evaluation sheets), 4 folders (Box 11)
    - 1983-1984. Big Ten Counseling Centers (Box 11)
    - 1984. Lesbian motherhood (Box 11)
    - 1984. Parents of gays (Box 11)
    - 1984. Sexual politics in the lesbian/gay male community (Box 11)
    - 1985. Opening doors to understanding and acceptance (Box 11)
    - 1986. Coming-out whole (Box 11)
    - 1990s general (Box 11)
    - 1991. Conference on the cultural construction of sexuality (Box 11)
    - 1993. What to do about nine and two: organizing to ensure Lesbian-Gay-Bisexual rights (Box 11)
    - Non-University of Michigan (Box 11)
  - Cornerstone Christian Fellowship 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Crisis intervention (crisis theory) 1984-1987 (Box 12)
  - Detroit Gay Liberation 1970 (Box 12)
  - Detroit. Task Force on Sexuality Discrimination 1978 (Box 12)
  - Dressel, James (Michigan H.B. 5000 prohibiting discrimination based on sexual orientation), 1983 (Box 12)
  - Episcopal Church Activities
    - AIDS
      - General (Box 12)
      - Remembrance and Hope service 1986 (Box 12)
    - Canterbury House (Box 12)
    - Diocese of Michigan
      - General (mainly regarding position of the church toward homosexuality), 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Canons 2003-2004 (Box 12)
      - Church and Society Committee
        - General (Box 12)
        - 1997 General Convention Resolutions Follow-Up, 1999 (Box 12)
        - Conscientious Objector (to War) 2001-2003 (Box 12)
          (includes several related issues of The Link)
        - Correspondence
          - 1982-1987 (Box 12)
          - 1995 1997-2000 (Box 12)
          - 2001-2002 (Box 12)
          - 2003-2004 2006 (Box 12)
        - Environment (attitude toward) (Box 12)
        - Financial circa 1977, 1995-2000 (Box 12)
        - The Link, 1997-2002 (scattered) (Box 12)
        - Meeting Minutes
          - 1976 1981-1985 (Box 12)
          - 1997-2000 (Box 12)
          - 2001-2004 (Box 12)
        - Native American Concerns
          - General 2000-2001, 2007-2008 (Box 12)
          - Racist Mascots 1999-2002 (Box 12)
        - Resolutions (Box 12)
        - September 11th 2001-2002 (Box 12)
        - Should Physician-Assisted Suicide Be Legalized in Michigan?-A Conference to Explore Issues and Concerns 1998 (Box 12)
          (co-sponsored by the Committee on Affirmative Aging)
        - Triangle Foundation Certificate of Appreciation 1996 (Box 12)
        - Various Issues 1996-2002 (Box 12)
        - Website 2002 (Box 12)
        - Convention address and newsletter (Box 29)
        - Correspondence 1977-1982, 2 folders (Box 29)
        - Directions (Box 29)
        - Impact (Box 29)
        - Minutes 1977-1982, 2 folders (Box 29)
        - Questionnaire 1977 (Box 29)
        - Resolutions, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Commission on Homosexuality 1966-1974 (Box 12)
      - Commission on Human Sexuality 1977, 1989 (Box 12)
      - Corporate Witness
        (later changed to Community Witness)
        - Assignment of Allocations 2000 (Box 27)
        - Funding Applications
          - 1995-1999 (Box 27)
          - 2000 (Box 27)
          - 2001 (Box 27)
        - Meetings and Correspondence 1999-2002 (scattered) (Box 27)
        - Ministry Fair 2000 (Box 27)
        - Resolutions 2001-2002 (Box 27)
      - Covenant V
        - General 2001-2009, 8 folders (Box 27)
        - Budget
          - 2003 (Box 27)
          - 2005 (Box 27)
          - 2008 (Box 27)
        - Charter Application -- Specialized Ministry Initiative 2005 (Box 27)
        - Extended Ministries Fund (EMF) Task Force II 2008 (Box 27)
        - Funding Applications 2009 (Box 27)
        - Homosexuality and Same-Sex Unions 1999 (Box 27)
        - Meetings 2006 (Box 27)
        - Millennium Development Goals (MDGs) Workshop November 10, 2007 (Box 27)
        - Ministry Fair May 5, 2007
          - General (Box 27)
          - Event Program (Box 27)
          - Peace & Justice Ministry Resource Packet (Box 27)
        - Resolutions 2001-2008 (Box 27)
        - Retreat 2006 (Box 27)
        - The Role of the Church in Public Policy circa 2003 (Box 27)
      - Curriculum on Human Sexuality
        - Early working papers (Box 27)
        - Borsch, Frederick (Box 27)
        - Correspondence and memoranda 1990-1992 (Box 27)
        - Curriculum materials 1991-1993, 3 folders (Box 27)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 28)
        - Readings (Box 28)
        - Review of Sexuality Curriculum 1992 (Box 28)
        - Robinson, Gene (Box 28)
        - Workshop evaluations (Box 28)
        - Workshop exercises (Box 28)
        - Workshop session I (Box 28)
        - Workshop session II (Box 28)
        - Workshop session III (Box 28)
        - Workshop session IV (Box 28)
        - Workshop session V (Box 28)
      - Death Penalty, Concealed Weapons Laws 1999 (Box 28)
      - Diocesan Convention
        - 164th-166th 1998-2000 (Box 28)
        - 167th 2001 (Box 28)
        - 168th 2002 (Box 28)
        - 169th 2003 (Box 28)
        - 170th 2004 (Box 28)
        - 171st 2005 (Box 28)
        - 172nd 2006 (Box 28)
        - 173rd 2007 (Box 28)
        - 174th 2008 (Box 28)
        - Resolutions Follow-Up 2002 (Box 28)
          (regarding tracking of resolutions)
      - Economic Justice Commission 1999-2001 (Box 28)
      - McGehee, H. Coleman (Box 28)
      - McMath Lectures 1986-1988 (Box 28)
      - Publications
        - Checkpoint: A Newsletter for Clergy and Laity of the Episcopal Diocese of Michigan, 1997, 1999-2003, 3 folders (Box 28)
        - The Record, 1974-2008, 2 folders, scattered (Box 28)
      - The Record Editorial Board
        - Budget 2000-2003, 2 folders (Box 28)
        - General 2001-2002 (Box 28)
      - Same sex marriages (Box 13)
      - St. Joseph's Episcopal Church (Detroit, Mich.) (JT was organist) (Box 13)
      - Task Force on Lesbian and Gay Concerns
        - General 1989-1992, 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Convention resolutions, etc. 1991 (Box 13)
        - Workshop 1992 "Sharing the Journey: a skills workshop for clergy and other church counselors" (Box 13)
      - Toy speeches (Box 13)
    - General Convention (75th) 2006 (Box 13)
      (includes material from 1996)
    - Homosexuality (statements, position on) (Box 13)
    - Integrity
      - Budget (Box 13)
      - Conventions/conferences 1980s (Box 13)
      - Correspondence (Box 13)
      - General (Box 13)
      - Meeting minutes (Box 13)
      - Newsletters and other mailings (Box 13)
      - Publications, speeches, essays (Box 13)
      - A Statement of Integrity Regarding Safe and/or Welcoming Congregations 2001 (Box 13)
      - By-laws (Box 29)
      - Convention/conference material 1980s (Box 29)
      - Correspondence 1980s, 7 folders (Box 29)
      - Meeting minutes 1980s, 3 folders (Box 29)
      - Newsletters and other mailings 1980s, 7 folders (Box 29)
      - Publications, speeches, essays, 2 folders (Box 29)
      - Reports 1980s (Box 29)
      - Resolutions (Box 29)
    - Episcopal News Service (Box 13)
    - Ordination of gays 1990 (Box 13)
    - Publications
      - General 1984-2005 (scattered) (Box 13)
      - The Witness, 1986-1987, 1997 (Box 13)
        (includes letters to the editor from John L. Kavanaugh)
    - Same Sex Marriages (J. Robert Williams information) (Box 13)
  - Galen smoker (complaint of homophobic content) 1994 (Box 13)
  - Gaub, Gary (writings) (Box 13)
  - GAWK (Gay Awareness Women's Kollective) 1973-1974 (Box 13)
  - Gay Academic Union 1973-1978 (scattered) (Box 13)
  - Gay Blue Jean Day 1978, 1981 (Box 13)
  - Gay Community Services, Inc.
    - Articles of incorporations, state reports, etc. (Box 13)
    - Committees (Box 13)
    - Establishment 1976 (Box 13)
    - Financial 1977-1978 (Box 13)
    - Gay Community Services Center (include Allen Ginsberg poster) (Box 14)
    - Gay Space (about publication) (Box 14)
    - Informational (Box 14)
    - Log books of Center 1977-1978 (Box 14)
    - Mailings/flyers (Box 14)
    - Minutes 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Newsletters (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
    - News clippings (Box 14)
    - Collection of documents re gay liberation, etc., 1 expandable folder (Box 14)
  - Gay counseling (include Legal Aspects of Gay Counseling), 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Gay counseling case files
    [CLOSED until January 1, 2096; files removed to vault]
  - Gay Hotline
    - General, 6 folders (Box 14)
    - Applications for training (Box 14)
    - Counseling referrals (Box 14)
    - Counselor-client relationship (Box 14)
    - Feelings about meeting, Fall 1975 (Box 14)
    - Logs (Box 14)
    - Orientation role-playing (Box 14)
    - Orientations
      - 1976 (Box 14)
      - 1977 (Box 14)
      - 1978 (feedback, etc.) (Box 14)
      - 1979 (applications and feedback) (Box 14)
    - Ready reference information (taken from binder in part) (Box 14)
    - Statistics 1979-1980 (Box 14)
    - Training miscellanea (Box 14)
    - Workshops 1975-1976, undated (Box 14)
  - Gay Liberation Front (mainly Ann Arbor; see also Detroit Gay Liberation)
    - General (Box 14)
    - Agenda CRD (newsletter); include calendars and news items, 1986-1994, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Clippings/press release (Box 15)
    - Correspondence 1970-1982, 3 folders (Box 15)
    - FOIA documents received from the FBI (Box 15)
    - Grant proposal for lecture series on homosexuality 1985 (Box 15)
    - Informational (Box 15)
    - Meeting agendas 1972-1976 (Box 15)
    - Meeting minutes (various) 1970 (Box 15)
    - Membership materials (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - Questionnaires (Box 15)
    - "Red Squad" files collected on the GLF (Box 15)
    - Workshop questionnaires (Box 15)
  - Gay Pride Week (later Lesbian-Gay Male Pride Week, and Lesbian and Gay Men's Pride, Awareness and Commitment Week)
    - Undated 1972-1994, 11 folders (Box 15)
  - Gay Radio Collective (Box 15)
  - GLOHRYA2 (Gay/Lesbian Organization for Human Rights-Ypsilanti/Ann Arbor) 1986-1987 (Box 15)
  - Homosexuality and the draft 1971-1972 (includes Jim Toy speech) (Box 15)
  - Human Rights Party 1972-1973, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Informational
    - Lectures on gay-related topics 1986 undated (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Published material (collected) (Box 15)
    - Questions asked about homosexuality (Box 15)
  - Lambda Health Project
    - "AIDS and You" conference 1983 (Box 16)
    - Constitution/bylaws 1982-1983 (Box 16)
    - Minutes/meeting materials 1982-1986 (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
  - Legal cases, bills, ordinances (Box 16)
  - Lesbian and Gay Law Students 1981 (Box 16)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights on Campus (LaGROC)
    - Announcements/flyers (Box 16)
    - Clippings (Box 16)
    - Correspondence 1983-1988 (Box 16)
    - Meeting minutes 1982-1983, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 16)
    - Scrapbook compiled by Carol Wayman 1984-1988 (Box 16)
    - University of Michigan bylaws (proposed amendment to guarantee non-discrimination on the basis of sexual orientation) 1983-1984, 1987-1990, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Lesbian-Gay Male Community Forum 1987 (Box 16)
  - Lesbian-Gay Male Community Action Committee 1987 (Box 16)
  - Lesbian/Gay Political Caucus of Washtenaw County 1980-1987, undated, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - Lesbian battering 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Lesbian mothers
    - Ann Arbor Lesbian Mothers' Collective 1977-1978 (Box 16)
    - Child custody issue
      - Clippings, poetry (Box 16)
      - Court cases (Box 16)
      - Legal issues, etc. (Box 16)
      - Social Work 509 class materials 1976 (Box 16)
  - Lesbian Mothers National Defense Fund 1975-1984 (Box 16)
  - Lesbian Network 1983-1984 (Box 16)
  - Lesbian Relationship program 1987 (Box 16)
  - Lesbianism (miscellaneous) (Box 16)
  - Library information (Box 16)
  - Lists of names for various organizations and groups (Box 16)
  - Little Lambda (gay youth group) 1979-1980 (Box 16)
  - Loulan, JoAnn, program 1986 (Box 16)
  - Manuscripts of dramatic presentations (Box 16)
  - Manuscripts, essays, etc. (Box 16)
  - March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights 1979-1993 (scattered) (Box 16)
  - Mesler, Ray 1979-1983 (Box 17)
  - Michigan Campaign for Human Dignity 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Michigan Counseling Center for Sexual Identity (proposal) 1974 (Box 17)
  - Michigan Gay Confederation 1972-1973 (Box 17)
  - Michigan Gay Undergraduates 1982-1987 (Box 17)
  - Michigan Human Rights Campaign (Box 17)
  - Michigan Organization for Human Rights 1974-1991, undated, 7 folders (Box 17)
  - Minuth, John (student who wrote anti-gay article for high school paper) 1989 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Moonrise (womens group) 1980-1983 (Box 17)
  - Moral Majority of Michigan (position re homosexuality) (Box 17)
  - National Coalition of Gay STD Services 1981 (Box 17)
  - Organizations (various), 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Ozone House (Box 17)
  - Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (Box 17)
  - Peer counseling 1974-1976 (Box 17)
  - Peoples Action Coalition 1978-1979 (Box 17)
  - Photographs (Box 17)
    (see also scattered photos in oversize box 22)
  - Pink Triangle Housing Specialists 1989-1990 (Box 17)
  - Poetry, chants, songs, etc. (Box 17)
  - Politics (various campaigns and issues) (Box 17)
  - Protests, demonstrations, complaints, etc. (flyers, announcements), 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Queers Action Committee (QUAC) 1984 (Box 18)
  - Questionnaires (Box 18)
  - Referrals
    - Peer/professional counseling and referral questionnaires, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 18)
  - Religion (miscellaneous)
    - Bible and homosexuality (Box 18)
    - Catholic Church
      - General (include information regarding Brian McNaught dispute) (Box 18)
      - Bead Reader, publication, 1973-1991 (Box 18)
      - Dignity (gay Catholic organization) (Box 18)
    - Clippings (Box 18)
    - Conference 1976 Gayness and Christianity (Box 18)
    - Evangelical Lutheran Church (Box 18)
    - Guild House
      - General (Box 18)
      - Announcements/flyers (Box 18)
      - Budget and financial (Box 18)
      - Meeting minutes 1986-1991 (Box 18)
    - Judaism (Box 18)
    - Lutheran Church (Box 18)
    - Methodist Church (Box 18)
    - Presbyterian Church (Box 18)
    - Publications and articles (Box 18)
    - Same sex marriage
      - Clippings (Box 18)
      - General information (Box 18)
      - Unity union ceremonies (Box 18)
    - Sexuality seminars (Box 18)
    - Speeches, essays, etc. (Box 18)
  - Religion (miscellaneous)
    - Unitarian Universalists (Box 19)
    - United Church of Christ (Box 19)
    - Universal Fellowship of Metropolitan Community Churches (Troy Perry) (Box 19)
  - Resource Room (proposal) (Box 19)
  - Resources for lesbian and gay male community (mainly Detroit area) (Box 19)
  - ROTC (protest of sexual-orientation discrimination policies) 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Sexual Orientation and Affectional Preference, Michigan House Subcommittee on 1980-1981 (Box 19)
  - Sexually Transmitted Disease (STD) Clinic 1980-1983 (Box 19)
  - Stonewall commemoration 1989 (Box 19)
  - Student Program Assistant in the Area of Sexuality and Homosexuality (SPLASH) 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Suicide intervention and prevention training (Box 19)
  - Thursday Night Coalition 1973 (Box 19)
  - Toy (James) personal
    - Appointment calendar 1991 (Box 19)
    - Biographical/clippings (Box 19)
    - Conference paper 1973 Gay Advocacy (Box 19)
    - Conference paper 1979 Gay Mental Health Issues (Box 19)
    - Conference paper 1994"'Desired under the Elms'..." re Lesbigay agenda for American colleges and universities (Box 19)
    - Course papers written (JT as a student) (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Social work career (Box 19)
    - Speeches/articles (Box 19)
    - Women's Study Program (JT was instructor for independent study on topics relating to sexuality) (Box 19)
  - Triangle Foundation 1991-1995 (mailings) (Box 19)
  - University of Michigan
    - Gay and Lesbian Alumni Association (GALA) 1986-1987 (Box 19)
    - Gay Rights Action Group 1976 (Box 19)
    - Housing (miscellaneous) (Box 19)
  - Wellness Network
    - Minutes, correspondence, etc. 1986-1990, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Volunteer training manual 1984, 1985, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Volunteer training 1988-1989 (Box 19)
    - Volunteer training June 1990 (Box 19)
    - Volunteer training November 1990, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Volunteer training February 1991 (Box 19)
    - Volunteer training June 1991 (Box 19)
    - Volunteer training, role-playing exercise (Box 19)
  - Wilder, Craig S. (Box 19)
  - Wolff, Eric. Essay: "Being gay in the Ann Arbor Public School," 1985 (Box 19)
  - Youth and youth liberation (Box 19)
  - Gay, Lesbian, and Straight Education Network (GLSEN)
    - Accreditation applications (Box 29)
    - Chapter history and by-laws (Box 29)
    - Goals and objectives evaluation sheet 2001 (Box 29)
    - Integrity (national organization publication) 2001-2002 (Box 29)
    - Minutes and correspondence 2001-2002, 4 folders (Box 29)
    - Minutes and correspondence 2004-2005, 2008-2009, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Newsletters 2000-2002, 2004-2005 (scattered), 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Programming 2004-2005 (Box 30)
  - Personal
    - Biographical information (Box 30)
    - Correspondence (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 30)
  - Ypsilanti Human Rights Political Action Committee
    - Correspondence and minutes 1999-2000 (Box 30)
    - Rainbow neighbors
      - Correspondence and minutes 1999-2000 (Box 30)
- Correspondence 1963-1995
  [The Correspondence series (boxes 20-21) is closed until January 1, 2021, except with the written permission of James Toy.]
  Correspondence (boxes 20-21; 1.3 linear feet) consists of Jim Toy's personal and office correspondence, dating from 1963 to 1995, with family, friends, and colleagues within the university, and associates who worked with him in various church and gay organizations.
  - General 1963-1995, undated, 25 folders (Box 20)
  - E-mail communications 1989-1995, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - With Gretta Locke 1975-1995 (Box 21)
  - With JT's mother 1975-1991 (Box 21)
  - With gay males in prison 1973-1993 (Box 21)
  - Christmas greetings 1975 (Box 21)
  - Easter messages (Box 21)
  - Greeting cards 1960-1994, undated, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Post cards 1970-1995, undated
  - Oversized posters and announcements (some include photographs) (Box 22)
    (see also oversize folder, Ac)
- Spectrum Center 1998-2004
  Spectrum Center 1998-2004 continues the documentation of the Lesbian-Gay Male Bisexual Office and its predecessor units. It mainly covers the Gender Identity Working Group task force, strategic planning for the office, and transgender issues and policies.
  - Gender Identity Working Group (GIWG)
    - 2001 Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - 2002
      - Administrative (Box 23)
      - Surveys (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - 2003
      - Administrative (Box 23)
      - Climate Research (Box 23)
        (social climate around gender identity issues)
      - Final Report (Box 23)
      - Surveys (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Website (Box 23)
  - Strategic Planning (STP)
    - 2005
      - Introductory Meeting July 16, 2005 (Box 24)